http://www.moneytreeinc.com/company/privacy/privacy-policy

COVID-19
As an essential services provider, Moneytree is open for business. Check out our COVID-19 page for more information and helpful resources. Please visit Locations for the most updated Branch hours as some may have changed.
×
Skip to main content.
State:
Search
Locations
Loans
All Loans
For state-specific Loan products, please select a state.
Check Cashing
Check Cashing
Business Check Cashing
Tax Check Cashing
Stimulus Check Cashing
Refer a Friend
Services
All Services
Contact
State:
Apply
Login
Locations
Find a Branch
Not your state?
Pick another location.
Contact
Search
Choose your state:
×
UNITED STATES:
California
Colorado
Idaho
Nevada
Washington
CANADA:British Columbia
By accessing or using this website, you agree to our Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy.
×
Choose a product:
Payday Loan
Installment Loan
×
Choose a product:
Payday Loan
Installment Loan
Moneytree Privacy Policy
“Great customer service
and fast service.”
Roll T.
Las Vegas, NV
This Privacy Policy supplements Moneytree’s GLBA Privacy Notice, which you can review by clicking here. In the GLBA Privacy Notice we describe our privacy practices for non-public personal information we collect in the course of our business of providing financial products and services to our customers. This Privacy Policy supplements that GLBA Privacy Notice in connection with our sharing of such non-public personal information with law enforcement officials, investigators and other third parties to investigate fraud, and in accordance with applicable law or legal process request. This Privacy Policy also applies to all other information (meaning information other than non-public personal information as described in our separate GLBA Privacy Notice) Moneytree may collect about you when you visit our branches or use our website and other online products and services that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”) or when you otherwise communicate with us.
Last Updated: 11/1/2019
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as by adding a statement to our homepage or by sending you a notification via email or otherwise).
Collection of Information
Information You Provide to Us
We collect information you may provide to us, including:
Comments, ratings and other feedback about our Services, including your name and any contact information you provide in connection with such feedback;
Contest and promotion entries, including your name and any contact information you provide in connection with such entries;
Any other information you choose to provide outside of the context of an application for, or use of, one of our financial products or services.
Information We Collect Automatically
When you access or use our website or other online products and services, we automatically collect information about you, including:
Log Infomation:
We log information about your use of our websites, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our websites.
Information Collected by Cookies and Other Online Tracking Technologies:
We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us to improve our websites and your experience, see which areas and features of our websites are popular and count visits. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.
We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our websites or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon.
Note:
We do not respond to Do Not Track signals sent from web browsers and so web beacons will continue to be used even if you enable Do Not Track settings in your browser. Online tracking may also be conducted by other parties. For more information about online tracking by other parties, please see “Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others” below.
Other Information We May Collect
Bank Account Information:
We may collect information about any bank accounts under your control in addition to the bank account information you provide to us.
Use of Infomation
We May Use Information About You for Various Purposes, Including to:
Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices;
Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by Moneytree and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests;
Process and deliver contest or promotion entries and rewards;
Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.
Moneytree is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.
Sharing of Information
All Information, Including Non-Public Personal Information
We may share your information, including non-public personal information we collect when you apply for or obtain our financial products and services, in the following ways:
In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; and
with relevant law enforcement officials or other third parties, such as investigators or auditors, if we believe it is appropriate to investigate fraud.
Please note that the above sharing descriptions clarify, rather than replace or modify, the notice of sharing we provide in our GLBA Privacy Notice. The sharing descriptions provided above are not intended to broaden or limit the sharing descriptions included in the GLBA Privacy Notice in any way, or otherwise limit our ability to share your non-public personal information as otherwise permitted under the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act.
Information Other Than Non-Public Personal Information
We may also share information about you, other than non-public personal information as described above, as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:
With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;
If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Moneytree or others;
In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and
With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.
We may also share aggregated or de-identified Information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.
Social Sharing Features
Our websites may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.
Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others
We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Moneytree and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and www.aboutads.info/choices.
Security
Moneytree takes reasonable measures to help protect all Information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.
Additional Information for California Residents
CCPA Privacy Policy
California Consumers’ Rights and Choices
If you are a California resident, California law permits you to request Information regarding the:
Categories of Personal Information (as defined by applicable California law) collected, sold or disclosed by us;
Purposes for which categories of Personal Information collected by us are used;
Sources of information from which we collect Personal Information; and
Specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
In addition, if you are a California resident you may:
Opt-out of the sale or disclosure of your Personal Information, in some circumstances;
Opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us; however, you may still receive administrative communications regarding the Services;
Opt-in to certain financial incentive programs we may offer related to the collection, sale, or deletion of your Personal Information; and
Request deletion of your Personal Information by us and our service providers, in some circumstances.
You will not be discriminated against for exercising your rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act.
Collection of Personal Information from California Residents
We have listed below the personal information we may have collected from California residents
in the past 12 months.
Category of personal information we may collect: Identifiers
Categories of sources from which we
may obtain your “Identifiers” include:
Directly from consumers, consumer data resellers.
The purposes for collecting your
“Identifiers” include:
To process customer transactions and for marketing purposes.
Category of personal information we may collect: Commercial Information
Categories of sources from which we
may obtain your “Commercial
Information” include:
Directly from consumers.
The purposes for collecting your
“Commercial Information” include:
To process business loans.
Category of personal information we may collect: Professional Information
Categories of sources from which we
may obtain your “Professional
Information” include:
Directly from consumers.
The purposes for collecting your
“Professional Information” include:
To process customer transactions.
Category of personal information we may collect: Educational Information
Categories of sources from which we
may obtain your “Educational
Information” include:
Directly from consumers.
The purposes for collecting your
“Educational Information” include:
To process employment applications.
Here is information on whether we sell or share your personal information.
Selling/sharing your personal information
Categories of third parties we may sell your personal information to.
We do not sell personal information to third parties.
Categories of third parties we may otherwise share your personal
information with.
Advertising networks, Data analytics providers, Operating systems and platforms, Consumer data resellers.
Requests
You can make requests related to your California privacy rights at the attached links:
Access My Personal Information
Delete My Personal Information
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
You may also make those requests by calling 1-866-556-1376.
Please be aware that we do not accept or process requests through other means (e.g., via fax, social media, email addresses, etc.).
When you make a request, we may ask you to provide verifying information, such as your name, email, or phone number. We will review the information provided and may request additional information via email or other means to ensure we are interacting with the correct individual. Please also be aware that making any such request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal or deletion of Personal Information or content you may have posted, and there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow us to fulfill your request.
Children
Our Services are not directed to children, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 16. If you learn that a child has provided us with Personal Information, then you may contact us as indicated above.
Do Not Track
Moneytree, Inc does not currently take steps to respond to browsers’ “Do Not Track” signals as no uniform standard to respond to such signals has been developed at this time.
Date created: December 18, 2019
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
Moneytree, Inc.
P.O. Box 58443
Seattle, WA 98138
1-877-613-MONY (6669)
Stay in touch. Receive updates about Moneytree products, offers and promotions.
